{"data":[{"question":"Shortly after the accident, two ___ police were sent to the spot to keep order.","a":"dozens","b":"dozen of","c":"dozens of","d":"dozen","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Dozen: Plural: dozen or dozens \n- Structure: Number + Dozen + Noun","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"60","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"We are going to review ___ today.","a":"Lesson fifth","b":"Lesson five","c":"The Lesson fifth","d":"Fifth Lesson","answer":"2","explain":"\n- We often say \" lesson five\", \"chapter two\"...","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"60","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"About ___ of the employees in that big advertising company are young people.","a":"four-fifths","b":"four-fifths","c":"four-fifth","d":"four-fives","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Four-fifths= four out of five ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"60","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"The rich farmer has raised ___ of ___ of ___ on his farm.","a":"hundreds, head, cattle","b":"hundred, head, cattle","c":"hundreds, heads, catties","d":"hundred, heads, cattle","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Hundreds of = Many, \n- Head of cattle= number of cattle","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"60","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"Thirty ___ died of that deadly disease last summer.","a":"thousands people","b":"thousand people","c":"thousands peoples","d":"thousand peoples","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Thousand: plural is \"thousand or thousands\" \n- People is plural of \"person\"","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"60","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"The hero and the heroine of the story are both artists in their _________.","a":"thirty","b":"thirtieth","c":"thirties","d":"thirty's","answer":"3","explain":"\n- In their thirties: age from 31-39","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"60","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"Robert served in the army in ___ when he was in ___ .","a":"1990s, the twenties","b":"1990s, his twenties","c":"the 1990s, the twenties","d":"the 1990s, his twenties","answer":"4","explain":"\n- In the 1990s: from 1\/1990-12\/1999 \n- His twenties: age from 21-29","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"60","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"When he moved to England with his family in ___, he was already in ___.","a":"fifties, his forties","b":"the fifties, his forty","c":"fifty, forty","d":"the fifties, his forties","answer":"4","explain":"\n- In the fifties: year from 51-59 \n- His forties: age from 41-49","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"60","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"___ of the students in our class are from outside our country.","a":"Three-fourth","b":"Three-forth","c":"Three-forths","d":"Three-fourths","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Three-fourths= three out of four","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"60","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"I've told you ___.","a":"hundred times","b":"a hundred time","c":"hundreds of times","d":"hundred of times","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Hundreds of = many","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"60","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"}]}